Guide to the Brooklyn playbills and programs collection BCMS.0041
Brooklyn Collection
- Hansa Theatre
  - Duty Is Duty (Dienst Ist Dienst) [2 copies], October 22-28, [no year] (Box 1)
    Program in German and English. "The Home of German Talkies" presents "Dienst Ist Dienst" with Fritz Spira, Ralph A. Roberts, Maly Delschaft, Heinrich Fuchs, Ernst Ducker, Fritz Schulz, Lucie Englisch et al.
  - Heart's Blood (Herzblut), December 3-10, [no year] (Box 1)
    Program in German and English. Gustav Froehlich, Renate Muller in "Herzblut." Story: Luigi Pirandello. Direction: Constantin David. Also with, Kitty Berger, Karl Walter Meyer, Fritz Alberti, Frigger Braut.
- Harold and Miriam Steinberg Center for Theatre
  - Napoli, Brooklyn, July 2017 (Box 1)
    Roundabout Theatre Company at Laura Pels Theatre, Harold and Miriam Steinberg Center for Theatre, Manhattan. "Napoli, Brooklyn" by Meghan Kennedy, with Shrine Babb, Alyssa Bresnahan, Juliet Brett, Jordyn DiNatale et al. Directed by Gordon Edelstein.
- Haverly's
  - Sharps And Flats [2 copies], December 19, [1881] (Box 1)
    Two advertising cards, each with a caricature of one of the leading actors in Sharps and Flats (Stuart Robson and William H. Crane). "Positively Last Week of the Comedians, Robson & Crane in 'Sharps And Flats.'" Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
- Hyde and Behman's Theatre
  - A Rube's Visit to Chinatown, September 6, 1897 (Box 1)
    Rice and Elmer, in their specialty, "A Rube's Visit to Chinatown"; Also with, Laura Bennett; Lawrence and Harrington; W. Gray's lateset successes; "Sergeant Hickey," by Edward Harrigan; and others.
  - Let Me Sing, October 25, 1897 (Box 1)
    Performances by The Carlons; Miss Liyyie Daly; Frank E. McNish with John J. Cain in "Let Me Sing"; Miss Phyllis Allen; Isabelle Urquhart, assisted by Sydney Wilmer and Walker Vincent, in "In Durance Vile"; Mr. Loney Haskell; and others.
  - H.W. Williams' Own Company of Entertainers, November 15, 1897 (Box 1)
    Performances by H.W. Williams' Own Company Of Entertainers; Fields and Salina; Charley Case; Smith and Fuller; Fisher and Carroll; John T. Sullivan and Company in Sidney Grundy's "Captain Huntington"; and others.
  - Post and Clinton, December 27, 1897 (Box 1)
    Performances: Post and Clinton; Chip, in his "Coster" and Character Songs; Miss Hilda Thomas, Vocalist and Comedienne, with Mr. Frank Barry; Edwin R. Lang, The Poetical Tramp; C.W. Bowser and Co. in the Farcical Sketch "A Domestic Cyclone"; and others.
  - A Supper For Two, January 10, 1898 (Box 1)
    Performances: The Premier Colored Performers, The Norrises; The Pantzer Trio; T.J. Farron; Mr. Bert Coote, assisted by Miss Julia Kingsley and others, in "A Supper For Two"; The Great Lafayette; Morton and Elliott; and others.
  - Vesta Tilley Vaudeville Co, February 7, 1898 (Box 1)
    Performances: Vesta Tilley Vaudeville Co., under the personal direction of Weber & Fields; The Musical Johnstons; Valmore; Reno and Richards; The Four Cohans; Miss Vesta Tilley; Chas. T. Aldrich; Lew Dockstader; Lamont Family; and others.
  - Big Double Show, March 14, 1898 (Box 1)
    Performances: Clifford & Huth and Caron & Herbert's, Big Double Show; Fields and Salina; Charles Case; The Three Polos; Fisher & Carroll; Smith & Fuller; Jones, Grant and Jones.
  - Miss Ambition, September 5, 1898 (Box 1)
    Performances: The Eldridges; Miss Hilda Thomas, assisted by Mr. Frank Barry, In "Miss Ambition"; Charlie Rossow; Miss Cora Tanner; John and Harry Dillon; Watson and Hutchings; Geo W. Day; Rossow's Midgets; and others.
  - Patchwork; or, Hamlet on a String, December 26, 1898 (Box 1)
    Performances: King and Cray, Chinese Acrobatic Eccentrics; The Martelles, Bicycle Experts; Cyr and Hill, vocal solos and duets; Nellie McHenry in, "Patchwork; or, Hamlet on a String"; Marshall P. Wilder; Falke and Semon; musical comedians; and others.
  - Going To Hyde & Behman's, January 23, 1898 (Box 1)
    Ad and program for Hyde & Behman's, "the leading vaudeville theatre of America." With Odell Williams and his Co.; Lydia Titus; Watson & Hutchings; T. Nelson Downs; Wm. H. Windom; The Donovans; Stinson & Merton; Powers Bros.; and others.
  - A Society Star, January 16, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances: The Three Glissandos, musical comedians; Merritt & Rozella, acrobatics; Harry Le Clair in "A Society Star"; Miss Maude Courtney, singer; Mr. & Mrs. William Robyns in "The Counsel For The Defence"; Fields & Lewis, Two Hot Tamales; and others.
  - To Boston on Business, February 20, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances: Baldwin & Daly; Miss Vera King; Chas. Wayne & Anna Caldwell in "To Boston on Business"; Hal. Merritt; The Donovans; Miss Ida Heath; John J. O'Donnel; Mr. & Mrs. Edwin Milton Royle; Press Eldridge; Baron's Lion Dogs et al.
  - The Rube's Visit to Chinatown, March 6, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances: Rice Bros. in "The Rube's Visit to Chinatown"; Ray L. Royce; Miss Gertrude Haynes; Flo Irwin & Walter Hawley in "The Gay Miss Con"; Miss Marie Jansen; Miss Marie Dressler and Walter Jones; Gus Williams; The Four Arbra Troupe et al.
  - Running for Office, May 22, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances: Caswell & Arno; Canfield & Carleton; Musical Johnstons; The Four Cohans in "Running for Office"; Ethel Levey; Bert Coote & Julia Kingsley in "Supper for Two"; Gilmore & Leonard; Three Fortuna Bros.
  - Between Matinee and Night, May 29, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances: Sadi Alfarabi; Hal Merritt; World's Trio; Chas. R. Sweet; Rose Coghlan, assisted by John T. Sullivan, in "Between Matinee and Night"; Al. H. Wilson; Al. Leech and the Three Rosebuds in "The First Lesson"; Nestor and Bennett.
  - Hyde's Comedians, September 18, 1899 (Box 1)
    Performances by: Hyde's Comedians; Three Fortuni Bros.; Jordan & Welch; Willard Simms & Jennie Graham in "Characters I Have Seen on the Stage"; Bobby Gaylor; Arthur Dunn & Clara Bell Jerome in "The Messenger Boy"; and others.
  - Coakley and Husted, March 5, 1900 (Box 1)
    Performances: Coakley and Husted; Howard Bros.; Harrigan; Camille D'Arville; Clarice Vance; Minnie Seligman in "In Paradise"; Press Eldridge; Dixon, Bowers and Dixon.
  - Circus Day in Rubeville, May 14, 1900 (Box 1)
    Performances: Leo & Chapman, "Circus Day in Rubeville"; Chevrial; Henri French; Pitrot; Camille D'Arville; Tom Lewis and Sam J. Ryan; Minnie Seligman in "In Paradise"; Josephine Gassman; The Chapmans.
  - The Folly Trio, January 6, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: The Folly Trio; Dooley and Fowley; Thos. J. Ryan and Mary Richfield; Collins and North; Scoot and Judge; Charles Wayne and Anna Caldwell in "Boston on Business"; Mortons; Artie Hall; Rosa Nayon and her Tropical Birds.
  - The Empire Show, January 13, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: The Empire Show; Kelly & Kent in "A Ginger Snap"; The Sandor Trio; Duke and Harris; Hickey and Nelson in "Twisted and Tangled"; Little Elsie; Hill and Silvainy; James J. Corbett; Sparrow; Gloss Bros.
  - Her Fifth Husband, January 20, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: Chas. Merritt and May Rosella in "Her Fifth Husband"; Thurman; Lillian Burkhart in "The Eighth Year"; Phyllis Allen; The Martinetti Family; Rice and Cady; "The Bachelor Club" by George W. Barnum; John Kernell; The Tossing Austins.
  - To-Morrow at 12, September 9, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: John R. Harty; Hamilton Hill; Gorman and Keppler; Elizabeth Murray; Kathryn Osterman in "To-Morrow at 12"; Elinore Sisters in "Adventures of Bridget McGuire"; McIntyre and Heath in "Man from Montana."
  - The Manikin Dance, November 4, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: Sullivan & Pasquelina; Katie Allen Fox in "The Manikin Dance"; Genaro and Bailey; Johnnie Carroll; Mabel Sisson and May Stewart in "A Mysterious Pill" by E. R. Burton; Jenny Eddy Trio; Clayton White, Marie Stuart Co. in "Dickey"; and others.
  - Reilly & Wood's Big Show, November 18, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: Reilly & Wood's Big Show; Purcell & Maynard in "The Bellboy and the Prima Donna"; Sisters Navette, Czarina & Girls from Maxims; Pat Reilly; Edwin Keough & Dorothy Ballard; Bailey & Madison; Leona Thurber & Co.; and more.
  - Adam the Second, December 16, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: Hyde & Behman's Orchestra of Soloists, Wm. E. Slafer, Director; Murphy & Slater; Lizzie N. Wilson; Matthews & Harris in "Adam the Second"; Howard & Burke; Hilda Thomas, assisted by Lou Hall, in "The Lone Star"; La Vallee Trio; and more.
  - All in the Family, December 30, 1901 (Box 1)
    Performances: Hyde & Behman's Orchestra of Soloists, Wm. E. Slafer, Director; Original Ford Sisters; Clipper Quartette; Eddie Clarke; May Edouin & Fred Edwards in "All in the Family"; Chas. B. Ward; Bellman & Moore in "Hester's Promise"; and others.
  - A Little Bit of Everything, January 26, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer and his Orchestra of Soloists; Brothers Farnum; The Yankee Comedy Four; Cook & Sonora in "A Little Bit of Everything"; Elizabeth Murray; Valerie Bergere & Co. in "Billie's First Love"; Louis Wesley; and others.
  - Clifford & Burke, May 5, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Clifford & Burke; Sullivan & Pasquelena; Matthews & Harris in "Adam the Second"; Talbot & Davidson; Four Nelsons; Bertie Fowler; Dempsey & Mack Co. in "A Man of Change"; John Kernell; Kiraley Ballet.
  - Too Much Woman, September 8, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Zazell & Vernon; Rae & Brosche in "Too Much Woman"; Lew Bloom; Matthews & Harris in "Adam the Second"; Merville, Booth & Elmore in "The Two Juliets" by Lawrence Sterner; Mortons; Yorke & Adams; and others.
  - The Gossips, September 15, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Hyde's Comedians; Ozay & Delmo; Boyce & Wilson; "The Gossips" by Charles E. Grapewin, with Louise Taylor, Victoria Wilcox, Fannie K. Dodson; The Colby Family; Trovollo; Piccollo's Midgets; Nichols Sisters; Tom Hearn; and others.
  - Why Walker Reformed, September 22, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Swan & Bambard; Falke & Semon; Milton & Dolly Nobles in "Why Walker Reformed"; Josephine Sabel; Cook & Sonora; Johnnie Carroll; Griffith Co. in a scene from "Faust"; Joe Welch; English Pony Ballet.
  - The Cole De Losse Duo, October 13, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer & his Orchestra of Soloists; The Cole De Losse Duo; Tim Cronin; Young America Quintette; Clayton White, Marie Stuart and Co. in "Dickey"; Edith Helena; Elinore Sisters in "Dangerous Mrs. Delaney"; and others.
  - Caesar's Angel, December 1, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer & his Orchestra of Soloists; Bruno & Russell; Leona Thurber and Pickaninnies; Edward M. Favor & Edith Sinclair in "Caesar's Angel"; Martin Bros.; Mme. Eugenie Mantelli; Mr. & Mrs. Jimmie Barry in "A Skin Game"; and others.
  - The Half-Way House, December 8, 1902 (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer & his Orchestra of Soloists; Swan & Bambard; Florence Bindley; Mr. & Mrs. Perkins Fisher in "The Half-Way House"; Maddox & Wayne; Miss Elita Proctor Otis in "A Bathroom Scandal"; Lottie Gilson; Guyer & Daly; and others.
  - The New Tutor, December 21, 1903 (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer & his Orchestra of Soloists; The Avon Comedy Four in "The New Tutor"; Fred. Gillet Trio in ""At a Theatrical Barber's.
  - The Military Maid, December 21, 1903 (Box 1)
    Performances: Eva Mudge in "The Military Maid"; James F. Dolan & Ida Lenharr in "Taking Chances"; Clifford & Burke; Dan Daly; Colby & Way; Tom Nawn & Co. in "Pat and the Genie" by Edmund Day; American Bioscope, lifelike pictures.
  - Herrmany's Dogs and Cats, November 13, 1905 (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer & his Orchestra of Soloists; Herrmany's Dogs and Cats; Lillian Le Roy; Eddie Girard & Jessie Gardner in "Dooley and the Diamond" by Wm. G. Rose; Carlin & Otto; Salvaggis; Sullivan & Pasquelena in Ä Newsboy's Appeal"; and more.
  - Christmas on Blackwell's Island (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer & his Orchestra of Soloists; Marvelous Frank & Bob; Leona Thurber and her Four Blackbirds; Emperors of Music; Sydney Deane in "Christmas on Blackwell's Island"; Lillian Tyce & Irene Jermon; and others.
  - The Labakans, December 17, 1906 (Box 1)
    Performances: Wm. E. Slafer & his Orchestra of Soloists; The Labakans; Irving Jones; Hugh Stanton & Florence Modena in "For Reform"; Nora Bayes; O'Brien & Buckley; Joseph Hart's latest novelty "The Crickets"; Matthews & Ashley; The Baggessens, and others.
- Imperial Theatre
  - The Dancing Girl, December 4, 1905 (Box 1)
    "The Dancing Girl"" a play in Four Acts by Henry Arthur Jones. Produced under the stage Direction of Claude H. Brooke. With Edwin Arden, Byron Douglas, Walter D. Greene, Frank E. Jamison, Alfred Keppeler et al.
  - The Butterflies, December 11, 1905 (Box 1)
    "The Butterflies" by Henry Guy Carlton. Produced under the Stage Direction of Claude H. Brooke. With Edwin Arden, Walter D. Greene, Frank E. Jamison, Alfred Keppeler, Marshall Farnum, James A. Boshell et al.
  - Delmore Sisters, December 3, [no year] (Box 1)
    Harper, Desmond & Bailey; Delmore Sisters; Dillon Bros.; Neil Barger & Co.; Alf. Holt; Ralston Grand Opera Trio; Frank Bush; Golemans; Kinetoscope.
- Keeney's Theatre
  - Old Man's Darling, September 26, 1904 (Box 2)
    Overture, Von Tilzer; Koppe & Koppe; Hazel Edna and Picks; Harry J. Breen; Watson & Hills; Corinne; Mason and Frances in "An Old Man's Darling"; Orpheus Comedy Four; Armstrong Bros.; The Keeneyscope.
  - The Prisoner, October 3, 1904 (Box 2)
    Overture, Hansen; Rennier and Gaudier; Carl Herbert; Talbot and Rogers; Kate Claxton, H. G. Lonsdale, Arthur Berthelet et al in "The Prisoner"; Mattie Lockette, Deltorelti Glissando; The Watermelon Trust; Rossi Bros.; The Keeneyscope.
  - Simple Life, January 23, 1905 (Box 2)
    Keeney's Popular Orchestra; Bowman & Bowman; Mlle. Olive; Hughes & Hazelton; Edward Harrigan and Co. in "Simple Life"; Yankee Comedy Four; Geo. Archer's Filipino Girls with Carita Day; Leroy & Woodford; Harding & Ah Sid; The Keeneyscope.
  - Her Friend From Texas, January 30, 1905 (Box 2)
    Keeney's Popular Orchestra; Curtis & May; Archer & Crocker; Messenger Boys' Trio; Lawrence & Harrington in "Instalments"; Edith Helena; Francesca Redding & Co. in "Her Friend From Texas"; Harper, Desmond & Bailey; Meehan's Dogs; The Keeneyscope.
  - Our Honeymoon, February 20, 1905 (Box 2)
    Keeney's Popular Orchestra; Gilbert & Burt; Harris, Cartmell & Harris; Nellie Florede; The Mignani Family; Lambert & Pierce; John C. Rice & Sally Cohen in "Our Honeymoon" by H. H. Winslow; Matthews & Ashley; D'Alma's Dogs & Monkeys; The Keeneyscope.
  - The Land of Two Moons, March 6, 1905 (Box 2)
    Keeney's Popular Orchestra; Bissett & Scott; Henshaw & Francioli in "Scenes in the Dressing Room"; Ila Grannon; Eckert & Berg in "The Land of Two Moons" by W. W. Prosser; Mrs. Annie Yeamans & Louis Wesley; The Harry La Rose Co.; and others.
  - The Nymph of the Sea and Queen of the Air, April 10, 1905 (Box 2)
    Keeney's Popular Orchestra; Watson & Morrisey; Martine & Balno; Adeline Frances; Naiada & Co. in "The Nymph of the Sea and Queen of the Air"; Fields & Wooley; Thomas T. Hayden & Co. in "A Young Old Bachelor"; Joe Flynn; The Woodland Nymphs; and more.
  - Darlings Animal Circus, April 23, 1906 (Box 2)
    Frank Keeney's Orchestra: John P. Hansen, Leader; Golden & Hughes; Josephine Davis; Darlings Animal Circus; Brooks Brothers; Little Garry Owen & Co.; The Great Victor; Billy Single Clifford; A Vine Cimaron Trio; The Keeneyscope.
  - A Special Meeting, April 30, 1906 (Box 2)
    Musical selection; Musical Huehn; The Three Graces; Lillian Shaw; Gorman & West in "A Special Meeting"; Nevins & Arnold; The Great Henri French in "Light in the Wilderness"; Jack Norworth; Wormwood's Bears, Monkeys & Dogs; The Keeneyscope.
  - We Heard What You Said, May 7, 1906 (Box 2)
    Music selection; Gartelle Bros.; Theo. Julian; Bowers, Walters & McIntyre; Gertie Reynolds; John F. Clark; Harry Vokes and Margaret Daly Vokes in "We Heard What You Said"; Majestic Trio; LeRoy & LaVanion; The Keeneyscope.
  - The Big Show: Story of Circus Life, September 3, 1906 (Box 2)
    Music selection; Hill & Hill; Mr. & Mrs. Billy Barry in "Reily the Plumber"; William H. Macart; Laredo & Black; The Messenger Boys Trio; "The Big Show: Story of Circus Life" by Edward McWade; Truly Shattuck; Piccolo Midgets; The Keeneyscope.
  - For Sweet Charity, September 10, 1906 (Box 2)
    Music selection; Arlington & Helston; Maxwell & Dudley in "For Sweet Charity" by Will M. Cressy; La Dent; Janet Allen & Company in "Phoebe Snow"; Nellie Coleman; Mrs. Stuart Robson in "The Late Mr. Wildoats" by Edmund Day; Adolph Zink; and others.
  - Case of Champagne, September 17, 1906 (Box 2)
    Music selections; Gallando; Francklyn & Eva Wallace in "Case of Champagne"; La Tour Sisters; Herrman, The Great, asisted by Marie Herrman; Morrisey & Rich; Mabel McKinley; Halley & Meehan; Holden Bros.; The Keeneyscope.
  - Managerial Troubles, September 24, 1906 (Box 2)
    Music selections; Kaufman Sisters; Henry Clive; The Musical Spielers; Huston & Dallas; J. Francis Dooley; Nick Long & Idalene Cotton in "Managerial Troubles"; Emma Carus; Miss Raffins Monkeys; The Keeneyscope.
  - Billy Barklay's Baby, March 25, 1907 (Box 2)
    Music selections: J. P. Hansen, Leader; Coogan & Bancroft; Melville & Higgins; Ethel Clifton & Co. in "Billy Barklay's Baby"; Ferry Corwey; Amelia Summerville; La Vine Cimaron Trio in "Imagination"; William Cahill; Bartholdi's Animals; Keeneyscope.
  - She Loves Me, She Loves Me Not, September 23, 1907 (Box 2)
    Music selections: Ernest A. Thornell, Director; Harlem Bros.; Hill & Hill; S. H. Wallach & Co. present Aubrey Boucicault & Co. in "She Loves Me, She Loves Me Not" by Byron Ongley; Mildred Hanson Dykeman; Katie Barry & Co. in "The Waiter."
  - The Girl From Yonkers, January 27, 1908 (Box 2)
    Music selections: Ernest Thornell, Leader; Green Bros.; Vera Sterling; Gilbert & Katen; The Great Eldridge; Vinie Daly; Mr. James Devlin & Miss Mae Ellwood present "The Girl From Yonkers" by Fred J. Beaman; George Evans; Baptist & Franconi.
  - A Personal Affair, February 17, 1908 (Box 2)
    Music selections: Ernest Thornell, Leader; Cogan & Bancroft; Marion & Deane in "A Personal Affair"; Deltorelli & Glissando; Leffingwell, Fletcher & Co. in "The Ashes of Adam"; Jess Dandy; Ned Wayburn's "Side Show"; McIntyre & McAvoy; and others.
  - Linda, March 8, 1908 (Box 2)
    Music selections: Ernest Thornell, Leader; The Pelots; Mr. & Mrs. Geo. Thatcher in "Linda"; Annie Dagwell; Brockman & Ford; Ameta; The Keeneyscope; Arthur Dunn & Marie Glazier in "The Messenger Boy"; The Kemps; Piccolo Midgets.
  - A Little Variety, March 16, 1908 (Box 2)
    Music selections: Ernest Thornell, Leader; The Musical Craigs; Trainor & Dale in "A Little Variety"; Jessica Lewers; The Rose DeHaven Sextette in "The Understudy"; Mr. Gus Williams; Nick Long & Idalene Cotton in "My Wife's Diamond's"; and others.
  - A C.O.D. Package, March 23, 1908 (Box 2)
    Music selections: Ernest Thornell, Leader; Malvene & Thomas; Adams & Mack; Jack Dempsey; Mabel McKinley; Marron & Heins; Wm. J. Sullivan, Clarice Pasquelena & Co. in "A C. O. D. Package" by Edward Weitzel; The Country Choir; The Mardo Trio; and others.
  - Just-Phor-Phun, October 19, 1908 (Box 2)
    E.A. Thornell, Musical Director; The Musical Vynos; Brown & Halvers; The Hanlons in "Just-Phor-Phun"; Daisy Harcourt; Violet Black & Co. in "In The Subway" by Edgar Allen Woolf; "Jack Norworth's Six Little Sailors" by Nora Bayes Norworth; and others.
  - A Prairie Flower, October 26, 1908 (Box 2)
    E.A. Thornell, Musical Director; La Dent; King & Brooks; Wm. J. Sullivan, Clarice Pasquelena & Co. in "A C. O. D. Package" by Edward Weitzel; Edna Aug; Varerie Bergere & Co. in "A Prairie Flower" by John E. Hazzard; The Willy Pantzer Troupe; and others.
  - The Police Inspector [2 copies], November 2, 1908 (Box 2)
    E.A. Thornell, Musical Director; Professor Allinei; Miss Leona Pam; Joseph Hart presents "The Police Inspector" with Percival Lennon; Fitzgerald & Wilson; Al Leech & His Three Rosebuds; Jeannette Lowrie; Elmer Tenley; Karno's Pantomime Co.; and others.
  - The Idol of the Hour, November 9, 1908 (Box 2)
    E.A. Thornell, Musical Director; Kirkpatrick, Smith & Emerson; Ed Morton; Horton & La Friska; The Three Cibelli Bros.; Virginia Harned presents "The Idol of the Hour"; Swan & Bombard; Carrie De Mar; The Borsini Troupe; The Keeneyscope.
  - Cherie, November 23, 1908 (Box 2)
    E.A. Thornell, Musical Director; Roland Travers & Co.; Marion & Heins; Ned Nye & Ida Crispi; Spensor Kelly & Frederic Rose; Clayton White & Marie Stuart present "Cherie"; Anna Loughlin & Joseph Howard in "My Sister's Big Beau"; and others.
  - The Banker and The Thief, December 28, 1908 (Box 2)
    E.A. Thornell, Musical Director; The Boldens; James F. Leonard & Clara Whitney in "Duffy's Rise"; Visocchi Bros.; Bunth & Rudd; Nick Long & Idalene Cotton in "The Banker and The Thief" by Ullie Akerstrom; Clarice Mayne; Matthews & Ashley; and others.
  - Stealing Home, February 8, 1909 (Box 2)
    E.A. Thornell, Musical Director; Rowland; Mabel Carew, assisted by Lucien Kecney; Tom Fletcher Trio; Carita; Lou Anger; Mabel Hite & Mike Donlin in "Stealing Home" by Vincent Bryan; James F. Dooley & Corinne Sales; Marriott Twins; Keeneyscope; and others.
- Kismet
  - Pastor Hall, February 23-March 1, [1941] (Box 2)
    Screenings of: "Santa Fe Trail" with Errol Flynn, Olivia DeHavilland; "Hit Parade of 1941"; Our Gang comedy, "Good Bad Boys"; Ch. 13 of "Green Archer"; "Pastor Hall" with Wilfrid Lawson; "Love Thy Neighbor" with Jack Benny, Fred Allen.
- Lafayette Avenue Presbyterian Church
  - Marianne Moore memorial service, February 8, 1972 (Box 2)
    An Act of Thanksgiving to Almighty God for the Life and Work of Marianne Craig Moore. November 15, 1887 - February 5, 1972. George Litch Knight, D.D., Minister. Includes hymns, order of service, a prayer written by Moore for her mother, and some biographical information.
- Lee Ave Academy
  - Mam'zelle!, November 23, [no year] (Box 2)
    Mlle. Marie Aimee, in the new comedy, "Mam'zelle!" By Messrs. Jessop & Gill, written expressly for Mlle. Aimee. Also with Russell Bassett, A. Del Campo, Leo Cooper, Newton Chisnell et al. Musical Director: A. Hinchcliffe. Stage Manager: Lester Victor.
- Lido
  - The Patent Leather Kid, April 22-25, [c. 1927] (Box 2)
    Richard A. Rowland presents Richard Barthelmess in "The Patent Leather Kid" by Rupert Hughes. An Alfred Santell Production. Directed by Alfred Santell. Production Management, Al Rockett. A First National Picture.
- Linden
  - Rolling Home, September 6-12, [c. 1926] (Box 2)
    Screenings: Reginald Denny in "Rolling Home"; "Social Triangle," the O. Henry Story; Corinne Griffith in "Into Her Kingdom; Also, "Mr. Cinderella"; Johnny Hines in "The Brown Derby"; Lloyd Hamilton in "Nobody's Business."
- Loew's
  - Beau Geste, October 13, 1927 (Box 2)
    Oriental Theatre: N. T. G. and His Radio Pals; On the screen, "Beau Geste" with Ronald Coleman; On the stage, "Among Us Mortals" with Mary Haynes; and vaudeville numbers.
  - Becky, October 17, 1927 (Box 2)
    Oriental Theatre: On screen, "Becky" with Sally O'Neil and Owen Moore. A Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Picture; Also, "Ben-Hur" A Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Picture; Vaudeville, The Parisiennes featuring Cully and Claire, with Garrick's Orchestra; Syncopators and others.
  - Two Lovers, October 29, 1928 (Box 2)
    Metropolitan Theatre: A United Artist's Sound Picture, "Two Lovers" with Ronald Coleman and Vilma Banky; and vaudeville. Loew's Bijou Theatre: Mary Astor in "Heart to Heart"; "Adorable Cheat"; "Beggars of Life"; "Tempest"; "Just Married"; and more.
  - Bought, October 10, 1931 (Box 2)
    46th St. Theatre:"Bought" with Constance Bennett; Cecil B. De Mille's "The Squaw Man"; vaudeville. Boro Park Theatre: "Daughter of the Dragon"; "Rebound"; "Convicted"; "Wicked"; and more.